你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
在上一个视频中，您看到了如何从头开始编译源代码并将其安装到您的机器上。
In the last video you saw how you can compile source code from scratch and install it on your machine.
这是了解和定制您的计算机上运行的软件的一个很好的过程。
And this is a great process for understanding and customizing the software running on your computer.
但对于大多数日常事务来说，这通常只是工作量有点太大了。
But for most everyday things it's usually just a bit too much work.
那么，如果您有一个可以浏览的软件库，并且所有的软件都已预编译并准备就绪，那又会怎么样呢
So what if you have a library of software that you can browse and have all pre-compiled and ready to
按一下按钮或一个命令就可以了。
go with a push of a button or one of a command.
这正是软件存储库和包管理器的作用所在。
Well that's exactly what the software repositories and package managers are for.
在这段视频中，我们将介绍它们的全部内容。
And in this video we'll be covering what they're all about.
在本视频中，您将了解可用的不同软件存储库
So in this video you're going to learn about the different software repositories that are available
以及如何使用在线网站搜索它们。
on the buntu and how to search them using the online Web sites.
在视频结束时，您将知道不同的存储库是什么。
And by the end of the video you'll know what the different repositories are.
您也知道什么是包管理器。
And you also know what a package manager is.
所以这堂课将会塞满有用的信息。
So this lecture is going to be jam packed with useful information.
让我们继续直截了当地谈吧。
Let's go ahead and get right into it.
好的，我们需要知道的第一件事是什么是软件存储库。
OK so the first thing we need to know is what a software repository is.
因此，可以将软件存储库看作一个装满软件的大库。
So think of a software repository as a big library filled with software.
然后，当你去图书馆的时候，你可以搜索你能读到的关于你可以看的书的书
Then when you go to a library you can search for books you can read about the books you can look at
不同版本的书，你可以比较哪些书你可能想借，然后
different versions of the books and you can compare which books that you might want to borrow and then
去图书馆借书吧。
check them out at the library.
软件存储库就像一个库，只不过您不必归还软件。
And a software repository is like a library except you don't have to give the software back.
更好的是，当出现新版本的软件时，您可以自动更新该版本
And even better when a new version of the software comes along you can automatically update that piece
的软件和整个系统上的所有软件升级到新版本，这些新版本可通过
of software and all the software on your entire system to the new versions that are available with a
简单的命令。
simple command.
这有助于保持您的系统的安全和可靠，也是完全史诗般的。
And this helps keep your system secure and reliable and is also totally epic.
现在，在BUNTU中有四个不同的存储库，每个存储库存储不同类型的
Now in a buntu there are four different repositories and each repository stores a different type of
软件，并在Buntu的主网站(Buntu.com)上对它们进行了描述。
software and they are described on the main web site for buntu which is a buntu dot com.
现在，如果我们去帮助Buntu.com，为劈开存储库创建一个大写的劈开社区
Now if we head over to help the buntu dot com for a slash community for Slash repositories with a capital
都是以其应收差饷入本而闻名的，顺便提一下，你在资源上放了个环节。
are known for its rateable into the capital you put a link in the resources by the way.
如果我们转到那里，我们将看到关于不同存储库的信息。
If we head over to that we'll see information about the different repositories.
好的，你可以在这里看到一个部分，上面写着什么是存储库，你可以在那里看到一个Buntu的存储库
OK so you see a section here that says what are the repositories and you can see that for a buntu there
有四个主要的存储库。
are four main repositories.
现在，主存储库是保存所有活动维护的软件的存储库，并且
Now the main repository is the repository that holds all the software that is actively maintained and
由Canonical和Canonical更新的是创造了Buntu的公司。
updated by Canonical and Canonical is the company that created a buntu.
现在，那里的所有软件都是免费的，就像自由一样，而且也是开放源码的。
Now all the software in there is free as in freedom and is also open source.
好的。
OK.
现在主存储库是最可靠的存储库，您应该尝试从合适的存储库中进行选择
Now the main repository is the most reliable repository and you should try and select from suitable
在可能的情况下，第一时间将软件放入主存储库中。
software in the main repository at the first instance where possible.
现在，第二个开放的存储库是语义库。
Now the second open to repository is the universe repository.
现在，这个存储库中的软件也是免费的，它也是开放源码的。
Now software in this repository is also free as in freedom and it's also open source.
然而，它不是由Canonical维护的，而是由Buntu社区维护的，因此
However instead of being maintained by Canonical it is maintained by the buntu community and as a result
因此，从理论上讲，它可能没有主存储库那么严格，也更容易出现错误。
it is therefore theoretically maybe less rigorous and more prone to bugs than the main repository.
但大多数情况下，这是非常棒的。
But most of the time it's fantastic.
根据我现在的经验，开放系统中的第三个存储库是受限存储库和限制性存储库
In my experience now the third repository in the open system is the restricted repository and the restrictive
存储库包括公司特定设备(如无线网卡)的专有软件和驱动程序
repository includes proprietary software and drivers for company specific devices such as wireless cards
诸若此类。
and so on.
现在，此存储库有助于确保计算机上的设备更有可能在
Now this repository helps ensure that the device on your computer are more likely to work out of the
盒。
box.
我们可以说。
Shall we say.
但软件通常是专有的，因此通常不会给你另一个软件的自由
But the software is usually proprietary and therefore doesn't usually give you the freedoms of the other
它给你提供的软件。
software it gives you.
此外，您可能能够也可能无法在受限的
Also you might or might not be able to directly examine the source code of the software in the restricted
存储库和这取决于。
repository and this depend.
这取决于特定的用例。
This depends on the specific use case.
第四个也是最后一个存储库是包含软件的MultiVerse存储库非驾车者存储库
And the fourth and final repository is the multiverse repository non-motorists repository contains software
这要么受到版权问题的限制，要么受到法律问题的限制。
that is restricted either by copyright or legal issues.
Multiverse存储库中的软件可能有也可能没有可访问的源代码。
The software in the multiverse repository might or might not have accessible source code.
您可以在这里看到，Buntu的理念通常是让用户选择使用什么软件
You can see here that the buntu philosophy is generally about giving the user choice about what software
他们想要利用。
they want to use.
有两个免费的开源存储库，一个是主存储库，另一个是通用存储库
There are two repositories that are free and open source which are the main and the universe repositories
还有另外两个资源库，它们在开源或软件所在的位置都不是免费的
and there are two other repositories which which aren't free at open source or where the software is
不太可能是这样的。
unlikely to be so.
因此，对一些人来说，使用非自由软件是可恶的，是完全不能接受的，而对另一些人来说
So to some people using non-free software is abhorrent and completely unacceptable whereas to others
如果它能完成这项工作就好了。
it will be fine if it gets the job done.
没有本图把这个选择留给你。
No buntu leaves that choice up to you.
但是如果像Fedora这样的发行版只在存储库中包含自由软件，而不包括
But if the distributions such as Fedora only include free software in the repositories and do not include
非免费的软件。
software that is non-free.
现在，这可能会造成减少不便，但它还有其他好处。
Now this could cause reductions inconvenience but it has other benefits.
现在，邦图让你自己选择你喜欢什么。
Now buntu leaves the choice up to you as to what you prefer.
现在，您已经了解了有关自由软件的辩论，您可以更好地进行选择
And now that you've been informed about the free software debate you are in a better position to choose
为了你自己。
for yourself.
现在我们了解了什么是BUNTU存储库，以及它们之间的区别
So now that we understand what the for buntu repositories are and the differences between them let me
带你去他们在网上闲逛的地方。
show you where they hang out online.
不，我不是指社交媒体，但是有一个叫做“包之门打开到.com”的链接。
No I don't mean social media but there's a link called packages door open to dot com.
因此，如果我们转到这里，我们可以浏览软件包列表，我们可以看到不同的
So if we head over to that here we can browse through the list of packages and we can see different
链接取决于我们运行的Buntu版本。
links depending upon what version of a buntu that we're running.
现在，每个新发布的Buntu的代号都会按字母顺序更改。
Now the code name will change for every new release of a buntu in alphabetical order.
举个例子，现在的这个叫作艺术性的土豚或简称为艺术性的。
So for example the current one is called artful aardvark or artful for short.
您可以看到您的发行版的代码名是什么。
And you can see what the code name for your distribution is.
通过在命令行中使用此命令。
By using this command in the command line.
打开您的终端，然后输入它。
Open up your terminal and you type it.
LS B下划线。
LS B underscore.
释放一个K，你给它一个选项，它就会。
Release a K and you give it the option and it will.
它将打印出有关您的Buntu发行版的所有信息，您可以看到我的信息名为
It will print out all the information about your buntu distribution and you can see that mine is called
可怕的食蚁兽，它在底部告诉我，这个代号很巧妙。
awful Aardvark and it tells me at the bottom here the code name is artful.
因此，我会单击您可以在此处看到的巧妙链接，打开查看适用的软件包
So I would click on the artful link which you can see here to open at see what packages are applicable
对我来说。
to me.
但是当你看这个视频的时候，你可以点击任何适合你的代号。
But you can click on whatever code name is appropriate for you when you watch this video.
好的，它的工作原理基本上是一样的。
OK it all works basically the same.
现在这里是所有包类别的包好的，所以你可以看到一大堆类别
Now in here are all the packages of package categories OK so you can see a whole bunch of categories
在这里。
in here.
您可以看到，例如，我们有用于Web服务器的东西。
You can see for example we've got things for web servers.
你可以看到我们有字体的东西，我们有编辑器，我们有文档数据库管理
You can see things that we've got for fonts we've got editors we've got documentation databases administration
实用程序和一大堆编程语言Peifer和文本处理视频。
utilities and a whole lot of programming languages Peifer and text processing video.
它就这样没完没了地继续下去。
It just goes on and on.
好的，这么多不同的东西。
Ok so many different things.
这些只是分类。
And these are just categories.
好的，这会破坏每个类别中不同的包。
OK so this blows the different packages inside each of these categories.
但是如果我们向下滚动，我们会注意到下面有几个重要的链接。
But if we scroll down we'll notice that there's a couple of important links down here.
我们有“所有套餐”链接。
We've got the all packages link.
我们得到了压缩后的文本列表，所以这里的这个只是一个。
We've got the compact compressed text list so this one here is just a.
如果我在新的选项卡中打开它，我们可以看到它只是一种文本文件，其中包含每个
If I open it in a new tab we can see that it's just a kind of text file here with a list of every single
其中一个包裹。
one of the packages.
我在准备课程的时候下载了这个文本文件，并通过字数统计命令运行了它
And I downloaded this text file when I was preparing the course and ran it through the word count command
并统计了剪切任何表头信息后的行数，发现有74000行
and counted the amount of lines after cutting any header information and found that there was 74000
还有六十个包裹，这太疯狂了。
and sixty packages which is crazy.
但你知道它就在那里等着你玩。
But you know it's there for you to play with.
我要关门了，但我们对这段视频不感兴趣。
I'm just going to close up but we're not interested in that for this video.
我们感兴趣的是这里的链接，它显示所有包，如果我单击它，它将打开
What we're interested in is this link here that says all packages and if I click that it'll open up
一个显示所有包的网页，所以让我们等待一下加载。
a web page that shows you all the packages so let's just wait for that to load up a second.
所以我们就到这里了。
So there we are.
现在我们得到一个网页，它给我们提供了到Buntu中每个可用包的链接。
So now we get a web page that gives us a link to each available package in a buntu.
您可能会注意到，它在方括号中显示了这些内容来自哪个存储库，所以我们
And you may notice that it shows you in square brackets which repository the things came from so we
在这里可以看到这个零高清软件包来自宇宙存储库。
can see here that this zero HD package came from the universe repository.
如果我们向下滚动，我们也可以看到一些来自其他存储库的内容
And if we scroll down we'll be able to see some that come from other repositories as well we see and
我们从宇宙储存库B.S.这里得到了很多东西。
we're getting a lot from the universe repository B.S. here.
我们有一个来自多重诗篇。
We've got one coming from multi-verse.
如果你发现一个包裹旁边没有方括号里的任何东西，那就意味着它是
And if you find a package that doesn't have anything in a square brackets next to it that means it's
从主储存库。
from the main repository.
举个例子，这里有一张自由党的长椅，你可以看到它旁边没有任何东西。
So for example there's a lib bench and you can see it doesn't have anything next to it.
这意味着它来自主存储库。
That means it comes from the main repository.
我想这也是需要注意的事情。
Guess that's just something to be aware of as well.
但是现在，出于本视频的目的，让我们继续点击顶部链接This This Package
But for now for the purposes of this video let's just go ahead and click on the top link this this package
一天打电话给零。
called Zero a day.
当我们单击它时，它会注意到一个新的网页打开，我们看到该包被称为
And when we click on it will notice that a new web page opens and we see that the package is called
身份证为零。
Zero ID.
我们可以看到包名或顶部。
We can see the package name or the top.
然后在这些括号中，我们可以看到软件包的版本号。
And then in these parentheses we can see the version number of the package.
然后我们可以在方括号中看到软件包来自的存储库。
And then we can see in the square brackets the repository that the package has come from.
正如我所说的，如果没有这样的信息，那么它来自主存储库。
And as I said if there isn't any such information then it's from the main repository.
好的。
OK.
正如我们所知，宇宙存储库包含大多数内容免费和开放源码软件，但它
And as we know the universe repository contains most content free and open source software but it's
由社区维护，不会收到来自Buntu开发人员的任何正式更新或维护
maintained by the community and doesn't receive any formal updates or maintenance from the buntu developers
在Canonical。
at canonical.
然后在下面我们可以看到一个名为Other Packages OK的列表，该列表与此软件包相关
Then underneath that we can see a list called other packages OK that are related to this package and
我们可以看到，在这里的括号中可能有所需的版本号。
we can see that we may have required version numbers in these parentheses here.
因此，例如，此DP K.G.包必须大于或等于版本1.1和5.6。
So for example this DP K.G. package must be greater than or equal to version 1.1 5.6.
好吧。
Okay.
您可以看到，有相当多不同的包与此相关。
And you can see that there's quite a few different packages that are related to this one.
好的。
OK.
你可以看到它们的前面也有一个特殊的标志。
And you can see that they have a special symbol at the front as well.
我们可以看到红色意味着它取决于这个包裹。
And we can see that red means that it depends on this package.
好的，红点表示零Adey包依赖于这些包。
OK so the red dot means that the zero Adey package depends on these packages.
这意味着要安装0 A.D.，我们需要安装前面有红点的所有这些软件包
So that means in order to install 0 A.D. We need to install all of these packages with red dots in front
他们也是如此。
of them as well.
如果我们希望零80正常工作，但是红点不是唯一可以出现在包裹旁边的符号
If we want zero 80 to work OK but the red dot isn't the only symbol that can appear next to a package
在包装较少的情况下，我们可以看到还有其他的符号。
in the package is less we can see that there are other symbols as well.
好的。
OK.
所以你可以在上面的钥匙上看到包裹旁边的绿色菱形表示AD为零
So you can see on the key up here that the green diamond next to a package means that zero A.D. would
建议您安装另一个软件包。
recommend you to install another package.
所以让我们把这个问题说得更笼统一点。
So let's make this a bit more general.
这就是你想要安装的软件包，这就是我们的案例0 8。
That's called a package that you want to install which is our case 0 8.
让我们称其为包裹。
Let's call that package.
好的，那么让我们将其他包列表中的随机包称为包B，即CAPE。
Ok then let's call a random package in the other packages list package B the Cape.
因此，如果A包推荐B包，这意味着为了使A包正常工作，我们
So if package a recommends package B that means that in order for package a to function normally we
应该得到包B，但是包A在没有它的情况下也会起作用。
should get package B but package a will function without it.
好的，那么蓝色方块会说a套餐建议给我们，还有其他套餐。
OK then the blue square would say that package a suggested to us and other package.
好的。
OK.
所以推荐意味着它不需要它也可以工作，但我们建议您正常使用。
So recommends means that it will function without it but we recommend it for normal use.
好的。
OK.
依赖意味着它不会起作用。
Dependence means it won't work.
如果您没有获得这些推荐的软件包，则意味着它将会工作，但不会像您预想的那样工作
If you don't get these packages recommended means it will work but not not like how you know it should
建议包只是一些完全可选的东西，你可能会想要检查的东西。
suggest package is just some entirely optional stuff that things you might like to check out.
好的。
OK.
最后一个是用黑点增强任何东西，这意味着它增强了
And the final one is the enhances anything with a black dot means it enhances the current package in
以这样或那样的方式，可能是新功能带来的新功能。
some way or another maybe new through New features.
但这也不是必需的。
But again it's not required.
好的。
OK.
如果我们向下滚动到这一页的底部，我们可以看到大小，我们可以看到包裹的大小
And if we scroll down to the bottom of this page we can see the sizes we can see what size the package
是下载，我们可以看到它的大小，当它被压缩并安装时，我们还可以
is to download and we can see what size it is when it's on compressed and installed and we can also
查看每个包包含哪些有用的文件，以便您可以单击。
see what what the files each package contains which is useful so you can click on that.
您可以看到每个软件包包含的每个文件的列表，并且可以看到不同的
You can see a list of each of the files that each package contains and you can see that there's different
适用于不同计算机体系结构的软件包。
packages for different computer architecture.
例如，如果您有一个计算机体系结构，作为EMT64体系结构，您可以下载
So for example if you've got a computer architecture that as an EMT 64 architecture you can download
这是一个软件包，如果你有一个适用于386计算机体系结构的软件包，你可以下载这个软件包
this one package and if you've got one for the 386 computer architecture you would download this package
您可以通过打开终端并键入您的名字DASH来查看计算机的体系结构。
and you can see the computer's architecture by opening up the terminal and typing you name dash.
好的，我们可以看到，在我们的虚拟机中，我们有。
OK we can see that in our virtual machine we have the.
我们在x8664架构上运行。
We're running on an x 86 64 architecture.
现在我64岁了，和X86 64岁一样。
Now I am 64 and X 86 64 are the same.
因此，我们会得到最适合我们这里的HMD64软件包。
So we would get the HMD 64 package is most appropriate for us here.
现在，如果您只安装了X86，那么您可以下载IDE 386软件包，因为它可能就是
Now if you just get X 86 then then you download the IDE 386 package because that's probably the one
最适合您的计算机。
most and most appropriate for your computer.
所以他们可能在想，等一下，齐亚德。
So they might be thinking wait a minute Ziyad.
等一下等一下。
Hold on hold on hold on.
你是说为了安装软件，我必须先搜索数千个软件包
Are you saying that in order to install software I first have to search through thousands of packages
然后找出它有哪些依赖项，之后我必须确保下载所有这些不同的内容
then find out what dependencies it has and after that I must ensure that I download all of those different
包并满足它们的依赖关系等等。
packages and satisfy their dependencies and so on and so on.
但在我下载所有这些之前，我需要确保它们都是正确的版本号
But before I download all of those I need to make sure that they're all the right version number and
这些软件包是否适合我的计算机架构。
that the packages are appropriate for my computer's architecture.
你一定是在开玩笑。
You have got to be kidding.
反正我也是这么想的。
Well that's what I'd be thinking anyway.
但不，好消息是您的计算机上安装了一个命令行工具，用于处理
But no the good news is that there's a command line tool installed on your computer that deals with
所有这些东西都被称为包管理器，而实际的程序与发行版不同
all of this stuff and it's called your package manager and the actual program differs from distribution
到分销。
to distribution.
但是在Buntu上，包管理器被称为apt，拼写为P，T，代表Advanced package top。
But on a buntu the package manager is called apt spelt a P T which stands for Advanced packaging top.
这就是我们要用来为我们做所有这些艰苦工作的东西。
And this is what we're going to do use to do all this hard work for us.
在下一个视频中，您将看到如何使用它。
And in the next video you're going to see how to use it.
但首先让我们回顾一下我们在这段视频中学到了什么。
But first let's have a review of what we've learned in this video.
在这段视频中，您已经了解到软件存储库有点像一个库，只不过是用来存储软件的
So in this video you've learned that a software repository is kind of like a library but for software
只是你不需要把软件还回去。
except you don't need to give the software back.
现在，对于其他发行版，它确实有所不同，但是在Buntu中，有四个主要的软件库。
Now it does differ for other distributions but in a buntu there are four main software repositories.
因此，这是一个主存储库，其中包含正在积极维护的免费和开放源码软件
So this is the main repository that contains free and open source software that is actively maintained
由Ubuntu开发人员提供。
by the Ubuntu developers.
也包含免费和开放源码软件的语义库，但它是由
Does the universe repository that also contains free and open source software but it's maintained by
社区而不是Ubuntu开发者。
the community instead of the Ubuntu developers.
有一个限制性存储库，其中包含用于设备驱动程序的专有软件。
There's the restrictive repository that contains proprietary software for device drivers.
现在，这个存储库中的软件不太可能是开源的，尽管它可能是开源的，但它并不活跃
Now software in this repository isn't likely to be open source although it might be but it's not actively
由开发商维护。
maintained by the developers.
最后是MultiVerse存储库，它的软件受到版权或法律的限制
And finally there is the multiverse repository that has software that is limited by copyright or legal
问题。
issues.
同样，该软件不太可能在MultiVerse存储库中是开源的，但它可能会
Again it's unlikely that the software will be open source in the multiverse repository but it might
就是这样。
be.
现在，有了关于自由软件、独木舟项目等的知识。
Now with your knowledge about free software the canoe project and so on.
您可以自己决定是只使用主存储库中的自由软件，还是使用通用存储库中的自由软件
You can decide for yourself whether you will only use free software from the main or universe repositories
您是否乐于使用来自受限的多词汇库的软件，但是
whether you are happy to use the software from the restricted on multi-verse repositories aswell but
把这个选择完全留给你。
to leave that choice completely up to you.
现在，当我们想要查看可用的软件包列表时，我们点对点地查看了两个软件包
Now when we wanted to see a list of packages available to us we headed over two packages dot to dot
com和位于参考资料部分的链接器。
com and a linker that is in the resources section.
如果您感兴趣，我们看到所有的包装都被我们的分发包拆开了
In case you're interested and we saw all the packages were opened were broken up by our distribution's
代号名称。
code name.
您可以通过使用以下命令输入lsp下划线Release命令来查看您的发行版的代码名
And you can see the code name for your distribution by entering the LSP underscore release command with
选项和我们看到的命令名称很巧妙，但您的名称可能会有所不同，这取决于您
the option and we saw the command name was artful but yours might be different depending upon when you
当你看这个视频的时候，把它下载给他看。
download it open to him when you watch this video.
现在，所有包都按主题或部分进行组织，您可以按以下方式查看包的完整列表
Now all the packages are organized by a theme or sections and you can see a full list of packages by
向下滚动到该页面的底部，然后单击相应的链接，他的包就会告诉您
scrolling down to the bottom of that page and clicking on the appropriate link and his package tells
在他名字旁边的方括号中告诉你它来自哪个存储库。
you what repository it comes from in square brackets next to his name.
但是它的名字旁边没有方括号。
But it has no square brackets next to name.
然后它来自主存储库。
Then it comes from the main repository.
当你点击一个包裹时，你会发现你会得到更多关于它的信息和信息
And when you click on a package you'll find that you get more information about it as well as information
有关与其相关的其他包的信息。
about other packages that are related to it.
现在需要其中的一些软件包才能运行该软件包。
Now some of these packages will be required for that package to run.
这些都标有红点和冰点。
And these are marked with a red dot and cold.
它们是您设置为依赖于这些包的一个包。
They are the one package you set to depend upon these packages.
其中一些是推荐的软件包，是正常运行所必需的，这些软件包将由
Some will be recommended packages and required for normal functioning and these will be indicated by
绿色钻石。
green diamonds.
有些是建议的套餐，仅供参考，并由蓝色方块和
Some will be suggested packages which are there just for interest and is indicated by blue squares and
其中一些将被称为增强，它将以某种方式增强包的功能，这些将
some will be called enhance that will enhance the packages functionality in some way and these will
用黑点表示。
be indicated by black dots.
最后，我们讨论了由于管理依赖关系和确保软件具有
And finally we discussed that due to the complexity of managing dependencies and ensuring software has
正确的版本号等软件管理通常使用称为软件包的程序来完成
the correct version number and so on software management is usually done using a program called a package
经理。
manager.
现在包管理器随发行版的不同而不同，但是在a上，包管理器被称为
Now package managers differ from distribution to distribution but on a to the package manager is called
阿普特。
apt.
也就是先进包装的意思。
Which stands for Advanced packaging too.
在下一个视频中，您将学习如何使用高级打包工具升级您的系统
So in the next video you're going to learn how to use the advanced packaging tool to upgrade your system
现在使用包管理器搜索新软件是使用新Linux系统的关键
and search for new software now using a package manager is a critical piece of using a new Linux system
幸运的是，这也是超级简单的。
and luckily it's also super easy.
所以，对于超乎你想象的不可思议的超能力，我将在下一个视频中见到你。
So for incredible superpowers beyond your wildest dreams I'll see you in the next video.